var questions = [
{
  question: 'What is known as Japanese horseradish?',
  choices: [ 'wasabi', 'nigori', 'mooli', 'ninjin' ],
  correctAnswer: 0
},
{
  question: 'Which of these is the name for geoduck?',
  choices: [ 'hokkigai', 'mirugai', 'akagai', 'tairagai' ],
  correctAnswer: 1
},
{
  question: 'What does \"sushi\" actually mean?',
  choices: [ 'raw fish', 'sashimi', 'rice with vinegar', 'seaweed and rice' ],
  correctAnswer: 2
},
{
  question: 'Which is not an egg?',
  choices: [ 'ikura', 'tamago', 'tobiko', 'awabi' ],
  correctAnswer: 3
},
{
  question: 'Besides water, what is the main ingredient in soy sauce?',
  choices: [ 'water', 'wheat', 'salt', 'soybeans' ],
  correctAnswer: 1
},
{
  question: 'Sushi is most closely associated with which Japanese city?',
  choices: [ 'Kyoto', 'Tokyo', 'Osaka', 'Sapporo' ],
  correctAnswer: 1
},
{
  question: 'Nori is: ',
  choices: [ 'green algae', 'blue algae', 'red algae', 'brown algae'],
  correctAnswer: 2
},
{
  question: 'What part of the sea urchin (uni) is eaten?',
  choices: [ 'brain', 'eggs', 'gonads', 'tongue' ],
  correctAnswer: 2
},
{
  question: 'Which of these is not tuna?',
  choices: [ 'Skipjack', 'Albacore', 'Bluefin', 'Hamachi' ],
  correctAnswer: 3
},
{
  question: 'Who is often considered the \"world\'s greatest\" sushi chef?',
  choices: [ 'Daisuke Nakazawa', 'Nobu Matsuhisa', 'Jiro Ono', 'Masaharu Morimoto' ],
  correctAnswer: 2
}]
